[{"answer": "Do you eat snails", "docId": "Man-Who-Knew-Too-Much_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "If you ever get hungry, our garden back home is full of snails", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Look, we only met him today. We can't expect him to change his whole life", "docId": "Man-Who-Knew-Too-Much_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Nothing! What's the matter with you?", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "my friend, I know you", "docId": "Man-Who-Knew-Too-Much_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "my friend, the big buyer from that place, was going to take us through the market tomorrow", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "my friend, you're setting a trap for me", "docId": "Man-Who-Knew-Too-Much_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You mean give him a change to be a doctor", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I'm so relaxed I'm tired. You take them", "docId": "Man-Who-Knew-Too-Much_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "my friend..", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "He was wrong. It was a different married couple", "docId": "Man-Who-Knew-Too-Much_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No. He found them. In the restaurant. Last night. That's why he was killed", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "No. He found them. In the restaurant. Last night. That's why he was killed", "docId": "Man-Who-Knew-Too-Much_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " That's just who it was, my friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Oh, yes, yes", "docId": "Man-Who-Knew-Too-Much_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " I have been my friend for nearby sevent", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I think this gentleman wants to talk to us", "docId": "Man-Who-Knew-Too-Much_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Humph! I have centuries of rest ahead of me", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Tell him...tell him everything. This is the time. I'm sure my friend is around here some place", "docId": "Man-Who-Knew-Too-Much_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I don't know how else to do it, honey", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "A pleasure, my dear sir...  I trust you will permit me to wait upon you tomorrow and to express the depth of my gratitude", "docId": "Man-Who-Knew-Too-Much_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " Oh but it was, my dear lady", "qsentId": 22}]